Guide to the Rice University James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy records, 1993-2014 UA 114
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XV: Edward P. Djerejian
  - Subseries E: EPD Trips
    - Paris September 11, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Washington/New York October 2, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Washington October 25, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - San Antonio October 27, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles/San Diego November 27, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - East Asia Trips, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Japan Trip-December, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Paris/London General Information, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Japan/China, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Preparation for June Paris Trip, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Council on Foreign Relations Washington Trip February 1-2, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Beirut/Lebanon Trip February 20-25, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Paris/London, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Persian Gulf Trip, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - January Visit to Israel, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Morocco Trip February, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Washington Trip-Morrocan Conference. April 26-28, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Qatar-June, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - United Arab Emirates June 17-19, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Japan Trip September 23-29, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Kuwait, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Center for Middle East Peace Trip Expense Tracking, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Syria-January, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Japan March, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - China March, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Cambridge Energy Trip March, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies-BIPP Meeting April 15-17, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Paris-Lafarge International Advisory Board April 24-28, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia May 9, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Paris-Republique des Idees Foundation June 18-21, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies White House Meeting June 28, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - London-Egyptian Council for Foreign Affairs July 8, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Paris-August, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Z's Folder-EPD Trip August-September, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Washington DC Trip November 10-14, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Washington DC Trip Fortune Global Forum, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - New York Trip Reimbursement, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Subseries F: Interviews, Conversations, and Speaking Engagements
    - Baker Institute Public Policy Course: Student Feedback, undated (Box 17, Disc 24)
    - EPD: Interview with Mike Wallace Transcript, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Ambassadors of the United States to the Middle East Tour, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - EPD Iraq paper-European Security Meeting Brussels, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - United States Policy on Arab-Israeli Peace Negotiations: Next Steps, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Saudi Arabia, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Syria, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Doug Schuler's Class March 17, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Latvia Letter (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Global Forum on Water, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Seminar on the Latest Energy Situation in Russia and International Energy Markets, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Prospect for Reform in the Middle East July 27, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Reflections of an American Diplomat February 9, 2006 (Box 17, Item 37)
    - Al Jazeera Interview February 20, 2006 (Box 17, Item 38)
    - Fox News Live February 3, 2006 (Box 17, Item 39)
    - The Future of U.S. Libyan Relations-HE Ali S. Aujali June 20, 2006 (Box 17, Item 40)
    - BBC Interview January 26, 2006 (Box 17, Disc 41)
    - Fox News Live January 16, 2006 (Box 17, Item 42)
    - Television Interviews: Israel/Hezbollah War July, 2006 (Box 17, Item 43)
    - CNN International November 1, 2007 (Box 17, Item 44)
    - Bloomberg Interview November 26, 2007 (Box 17, Item 45)
    - CBS Clip on Charlie Wilson's War December 19, 2007 (Box 17, Item 46)
    - Bloomberg: Iranian Missile Crisis Interview July 9, 2008 (Box 17, Item 47)
    - Bloomberg TV: Israel and Syria July 29, 2008 (Box 17, Item 48)
    - O-Week Freshman Address August 18, 2008 (Box 17, Disc 49)
    - HRi Radio Show The Jim Bohannon Show September 12, 2008 (Box 17, Disc 50)
    - Danger and Opportunity: An American Ambassador's Journey Through the Middle East September 23, 2008 (Box 17, Disc 51)
    - The City Club of Cleveland August 7, 2009 (Box 17, Item 52)
    - CNN-Anderson Cooper 360 May 27, 2010 (Box 17, Item 53)
    - Marketplace Morning Report June 15, 2010 (Box 17, Item 54)
    - PRI's The World November 29, 2010 (Box 17, Item 55)
    - Michael Doran Interviews Edward P. Djerejian December 20, 2010 (Box 17, Item 56)
    - NPR's Talk of the Nation-President Obama to Clarify Mission in Libya March 28, 2011 (Box 17, Item 57)
    - Bloomberg Bottom Line May 2, 2011 (Box 17, Item 58)
    - On China with author The Honorable Henry A. Kissinger June 16, 2011 (Box 17, Item 59)
    - Key Television Appearances, 2011 (Box 17, Item 60)
    - Interview with George H.W. Bush by Edward P. Djerejian October 20, 2011 (Box 17, Item 61)
    - A Conversation with Lietenant General (Retired) Brent Scowcroft April 4, 2012 (Box 17, Item 62)
  - Subseries G: BIPP Events
    - BIPP Events Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - United States-Mexican Relations and Implications for Hemispheric Trade Corporate Executive Seminar, 1 of 2, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - United States-Mexican Relations and Implications for Hemispheric Trade Corporate Executive Seminar, 2 of 2, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Shell Distinguished Lecture Series U.N. Secretary-General Boutros Boutros-Ghali Speaks on the United Nations and Peacekeeping May 25, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - China, the United States, and Asia: Challenges for US Policy and Business Conference Planning, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Newspapers and News Clippings, 1995-2016 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - China, the United States, and Asia: Challenges for US Policy and Business Conference February 9-10, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Shell Distinguished Lecture Series Yasser Arafat, President of the Palestine National Authority March 5, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Crown Prince Abdullah Visit, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - King Abdullah II May 9, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Energy and Nanotechnology Storage and the Grid November 15-16, 2005 (Box 18, Item 12)
    - Happy Birthday, Mr. Secretary-75th Birthday of James A. Baker III April 28, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - American Vertigo: Traveling America in the Footsteps of Tocqueville February 13, 2006 (Box 18, Item 14)
    - The Honorable William J. Clinton February 8, 2007 (Box 18, Item 15)
    - Women in the Middle East: A Contemporary Assessment May 21, 2007 (Box 18, Item 16)
    - Negotiating Jerusalem October 25, 2007 (Box 18, Item 17)
    - The Arab World: History, Culture, and Politics Lecture Series November 1, 2007 (Box 18, Item 18)
    - Nuclear Nonproliferation November 10, 2007 (Box 18, Item 19)
    - NATO: The Balkans, Afghanistan and Beyond December 10, 2007 (Box 18, Item 20)
    - Town Hall Forum the Honorable John McCain February 28, 2008 (Box 18, Item 21)
    - Religion in the Elections, 1 of 2, April 7, 2008 (Box 18, Disc 22)
    - Religion in the Elections, 2 of 2, April 7, 2008 (Box 18, Disc 22)
    - Vecinos Lecture Series: A New Deal for a New Age April 28, 2008 (Box 18, Item 24)
    - Mt. Everest Video Conference May 18, 2008 (Box 18, Item 25)
    - Campaign 2008: The Issues Considered The Next President and Foreign Policy: One Republican's Perspective October 14 (Box 18, Item 26)
    - 15th Anniversary, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Berlin Wall Event, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Item 28)
    - What FDR Can Teach President Obama... and the Rest of Us April 17, 2009 (Box 18, Item 29)
    - Roundtable Annual Dinner Remarks May 4, 2009 (Box 18, Disc 30)
    - Roundtable Annual Dinner Questions and Answers May 4, 2009 (Box 18, Disc 31)
    - President Mahmoud Abbas August 21, 2009 (Box 18, Item 32)
    - German Unification: Expectations and Outcomes, Panel Discussion October 30, 2009 (Box 18, Item 33)
    - Diplomacy in Iraq November 4, 2009 (Box 18, Item 34)
    - Stem Cell Theory and Practice January 5-9, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - The Pickens Plan January 6, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Diplomatic Corps Visit January 9, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Mapping the Human Genome: A Dialogue on Science and Public Life January 21, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Roundtable on Houston's Preparedness for Terrorism and Catastrophic Natural Disasters January 27, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Fiscal Wake-Up Tour January 29, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Civic Scientist Lecture Series: Comparing Scientific Controversy with Public Controversy; Engaging Our Future Generation of Scientists October 13, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Life After Ike: The Future of Houston and Galveston March 11, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Baker Institute Doha and Moscow Trip March 13-20, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Peace in the Middle East: Lessons Learned and New Directions March 24, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - America and China: The Next 30 Years April 2-3, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Science Collaborations Across Borders April 27, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Ambassadresses at Large: Partners in Diplomacy April 21, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - National Healthcare Reform: Strategies for a Country in Crisis May 6, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Russia and the Caspian States in the Global Energy Balance Discussion May 6-7, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Women as Agents of Change in the Middle East May 8, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The Israeli-Palestinian Peace Process: Four Narratives and a Five-Component Strategy May 12, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 3rd International Space Medicine Summit May 14-17, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - 80th Birthday April 24, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Civic Scientist Lecture Series: Comparing Scientific Controversy with Public Controversy; Engaging Our Future Generation of Scientists October 13, 2010 (Box 19, Item 14)
    - Congratulatory Correspondence and Thank You Notes, 2010-2022 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - No Higher Honor: A Memoir of My Years in Washington November 8, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Global Affairs and the Global Economy April 11, 2012 (Box 19, Item 17)
    - 20th Anniversary Gala Celebration, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Djerejian Retirement, 2021 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Subseries H: EPD Events
    - Speaking Events, 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Speaking Events, 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Speeches, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Alfalfa Club Dinner, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Preston Moore Lunch, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Taylor-Smith Group Town Hall Breakfast, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - JETRO, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Mayor Lanier Visit February 3, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Electric Power Executive Breakfast February 7, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - JINSA Breakfast March 8, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Public Affairs Officers Breakfast March 21, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Town and Gown Society April 25, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Beaumont Rotarians August 30, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Kincaid School October 11, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - American Society for Legal History October 19-22, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Magic Circle of Republican Women October 23, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Consular Ball October 28, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - The Oilmakers Reception December 12, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Laureates Dinner Rice Alumni Gold Medal Award May 9, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Subseries I: General Correspondence
    - General Correspondence, 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1 of 3, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2 of 3, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 3 of 3, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - EPD General Correspondence, 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - EPD Correspondence Gillis, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - EPD Remarks from the Conference on China, the United States, and Asia: Challenges for US Policy and Business, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 10th Anniversary Correspondence and Supplementary Documents, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Secretary Baker's 80th Birthday Event Planning Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Subseries J: Building Files
    - BIPP Building Preliminary Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Building Correspondence, 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Building Correspondence, 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Building Committee Minutes, 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Building Committee Minutes, 2 of 2, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Construction Bidders, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Century Development, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Shell Space, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - BIPP-A.Z. Parks, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Baker Project Trailer Selects, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - EPD-Desk-Building File, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Building Correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Century Development Status Reports 1 of 4, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Century Development Status Reports 2 of 4, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Century Development Status Reports 3 of 4, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Century Development Status Reports 4 of 4, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Contractor: Morganti Texas, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Building, 1 of 2, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Building, 2 of 2, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - BIPP Building-Interior Designs, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Quotation Panels-Mosaics, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Various Conceptual Plans and Building Correspondence, 1 of 4, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Various Conceptual Plans and Building Correspondence, 2 of 4, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Various Conceptual Plans and Building Correspondence, 3 of 4, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Various Conceptual Plans and Building Correspondence, 4 of 4, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Contingency, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - BIPP Building-Detail Issues, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Telecommunications, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Building-Donor Graphics, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Subseries K: Counter Terrorism
    - Correspondence, 1 of 3, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2 of 3, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 3 of 3, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings, Notes, and Communications, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Counter Terrorrism Information, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Joint BIPP-Center for Strategic and International Studies Counter Terrorism Task Force, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Subseries L: Council on Foreign Relations
    - National Interests Project, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1996-2005 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on America's Response to Terror Background Materials for Inaugural Meeting, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Improving the U.S. Public Diplomacy Campaign of the War Against Terrorism, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - CFR Task Force Report and Press Release August, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Former Secretaries of State Panel May 6, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Iraq: The Day After-Video Conference January 16, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Working Group on Arabian Gulf October 7, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Iraq: One Year After, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Subseries M: Conflict Resolution
    - Israel-Syria Information File, 1 of 3, 1995-2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Israel-Syria Information File, 2 of 3, 1995-2003 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Israel-Syria Information File, 3 of 3, 1995-2003 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Notes and Contact Info, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Nagarno Karabagh, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Reading, 1997-2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Armenian Public Rally September 24, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Peter Rosenblatt Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Baku, Azerbajian, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Yerevan, Armenia, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - OCSE Briefing Papers, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Armenia-Manoukian, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Armenia, 2000-2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - US-Syrian Dialogue, 1 of 2, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - US-Syrian Dialogue, 2 of 2, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - The Middle East and the Quest for Arab-Israeli Peace: Considerations for United States Policy, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Geneva Accord Letter, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Israeli-Palestinian Poll, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Israeli-Palestinian Workshop, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Salam Fayyad, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Israeli-Palestinian Workshop Study, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Mahmoud Abbas, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Qatar Response, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Remarks to the Armenian Reporter International Fortieth Anniversary Gala, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Syria, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - BIPP Israeli-Palestinian Workshop, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Israel-Palestine Washington DC, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Peres Peace Project, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Hirschfield Proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Economic Cooperation Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Preparations for July Visit to Jerusalem, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Armenia, 2011-2013 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Arab-Israeli Conflict Workshop, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Subseries N: Access Files
    - Middle East Reports and Lectures, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Press Coverage, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Baker Institute 12 Month Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - George Bush Presidential Library Foundation, 1993-1998 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Baylor-Baker Chair, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - BIPP Documentary, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Clarence Carter Chair, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Media-Press Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Joint Ventures-General, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Media-Press Clips, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Director Appointment and Continuation Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - EPD Press Clippings and Coverage, 1994-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - School of Continuing Studies-United Nations at 50 "The Future: Where Do We Go from Here" May 8, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Baker Book Tour, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Press Coverage, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - "A Stateman's Story" Video-Correspondence, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Annual Conference Speakers-Colin Powell, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Chair in Islamic Economics, Finance, and Management, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Chair in Middle Eastern and Central Asian Studies, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Assistant Vice President of Development, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - JAB III Invitations, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Secretary Baker Interviews, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Tax Policy Unit, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Op-ed Articles by EPD, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - BIPP Thatcher, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Secretary Baker Testimony to Senate Armed Services Committee September 12, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Research Fellow Search, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Department Coordinator Search, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Office Assistant Search, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - EPD Correspondence Baker-Djerejian, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - BIPP-General Alexander Lebed, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Israel and Syria: The Strategic Function of Middle East Peace Article, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Press Coverage and Clippings, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Translation Pieces for Letters and Articles, 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - The Arc of Crisis-The Challenge to US Foreign Policy Article, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Institute Administrator Search, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Kozyrev-Baker Event Meeting February 16, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Middle East-General, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - EPD Correspondence Baker-Djerejian, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Events Coordinator Search, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Office Assistant Search, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Executive Assistant Search, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Baker Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Requests for EPD, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Student Aid Foundation Enterprises, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Southern Illinois University Carbondale, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Syria and Israel: Eliminate the Negative Article, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Perspective on Middle East Article, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Japan Foundation, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - His Excellency (HE) Shiek Hamad Bin Jassim Bin Jaber Al Thani Correspondence, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Concerning Communications, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - EPD Event Remarks and Clippings, 2005-2016 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 1 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 2 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 3 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 4 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 5 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 6 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Getting to the Territorial Endgame of an Israeli-Palestinian Peace Settlement Work, 7 of 7, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Series XVI: Rice University Boards
  - Subseries A: Board of Governors
    - Board Meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Board Meetings, 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Board Meetings, 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Board of Trustees
    - Board Meetings, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Board Meetings, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Board Meetings and Related Commissions, 2000-2007 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series XVII: Digital archive of materials not represented physically
  - Subseries A: Documents and photographs
    - James A. Baker III awards, Circa 1990-2015
      Scope and Contents
      PDF documents which represent award certificates and photos of physical awards. Example awards included are .......
    - Major events at Baker Institute: Conferences and Summits, 1995